<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Matías Moreno</title>
    <link>https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Matías Moreno</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Inventory</title>
      <link>https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/artificial-inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/artificial-inventory/</guid>
      <description>Project presented in &amp;ldquo;Feria de Software USM 2020&amp;rdquo;. We developed a system that uses the direct feed from security cameras, to process the images and identify empty spaces and people in shelves of a pet supply store, using convolutional neural networks in real time.
Image segmentation We used image segmentation to detect empty areas in the store, also we used the position to identify the product.
      Some of my performed tasks included:  Product owner and data scientist of the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle routing and collection optimization</title>
      <link>https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/route-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matiasmoreno.github.io/portfolio/projects/route-optimization/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science Engineering thesis. Design and development of metaheuristic technique that allows finding solutions to the Milk Collection Problem with Selection and Blending.
Vehicle Routing Problem The Vehicle Routing Problem is a combinational optimization and integer programming problem wich asks &amp;ldquo;What is the optimal set of routes for a fleet of vehicles to traverse in order to deliver to a given set of customers?&amp;rdquo;.
  In my Computer Science engineering thesis I designed and tested a two-stage metaheuristic technique, that finds efficient routes for large routing instances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
